Tarık KAMAT

contact@tarikkamat.com • github.com/tarikkamat

Back-End Developer

Aiming for a good career for himself. Feeling ready to work for his goals. Not afraid to do research and learn new things. Self-taught and high motivation developer, among the top 10% graduates in the Kodluyoruz PHP Laravel Bootcamp.

Specialties: PHP, C#, Java and, Swift.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS, Laravel, .NET, Terminal, Npm, Yarn, Brew

Languages: English (B1), Turkish (Native)

Programming resources used for self-learning: Document, Udemy, Stack Overflow

Achievements:

Kodluyoruz - PHP Laravel / Success Certificate,

Patika - iOS Swift / Student,

Interests: Fitness

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Eanship Teknoloji A.Ş, Istanbul	Aug 2022 - Current
---------------------------------	--------------------

Software Developer

- Supported both the web design and interface in the frontend, and the web projects connections with the server and database section in the backend;
- Converted design to code using technologies such as PHP, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.

	Natro, Istanbul	Aug 2021 - Apr 2022
--	-----------------	---------------------

Helpdesk

- I assisted customers in server, hosting and domain name management issues, including written or in-call problems.
- I gained knowledge on Linux, cPanel, Plesk.

Intern, Wordpress Developer

- In the software department, I contributed to the development of specially developed plugins to increase the wordpress experience.
- Payment plugins, marketplace integration plugins etc.

EDUCATION AND COURSES

Software Engineering (B.Sc.), Zaim University, Istanbul	2022
Computer Programming (A.A.), Duzce University, Duzce	2019 - 2021
• Graduated among top 10% of the class	
• GPA: 3.35/4.00	
Kodluyoruz PHP Laravel Bootcamp, Istanbul	Jan 2021
Patika iOS Swift Bootcamp, Istanbul	Aug 2022

PROJECTS

Personal Blog App Jan 2	Personal Blog App	Jan 2021
-------------------------	-------------------	----------

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, Laravel

Features: Adding, removing, editing, updating operations are performed for Category, Tag, Article. View, approve/disapprove, delete comments. Forms are validated. User login and logout operations. SweetAlert2 for notification system.

Other projects on my GitHub profile